Okay, so it looks like you've already updated the kind of closing date and everything else.
So adding questions. Adding questions comes from here. We'll have to change the maximum
grade to 30 because it's 30 questions first. We won't shuffle because there's question
numbers in there, so we'll have to confuse them, but you know, probably not too much
of an issue. And then for the question bank. And this is where you needed to go. So it's
the default for six ACS because there's 30 questions in there. I've checked them against
the current ones, which technique would separate, which technique would separate. If I do show
all as well. It looks like it's quite odd because obviously it does it by number, which
is a bit strange, but there we go. So you then select all those, add selected questions
to quiz. Now you could fluff about and re-sort all these. Probably better just to remove
the question number, but it is what it is. If you re-paginate though, to have unlimited
questions per page, that will then mean that essentially they can just scroll through all
the questions. You could re-sort all these, but I don't know how much value is in that.
But yeah, I'll probably end up sorting it because I can't help it. I'll be a bit anal
about it. So I'll re-sort all those. And then you just save. And then if we go back to the
quiz then, and we preview quiz, tell me I've started it. The quizzes in there then. In
fact, it doesn't look like I need to re-sort, does it? No, that's quite useful. Because
the number doesn't come up. That's quite useful. Didn't even need to sort it. That's fine.
So I will update that. If I go back to that, probably. Yeah, I can go there. Can I change
the name? Settings, no longer empty. And I'll figure out how to either password now. So
I'll be the next bit. One important thing you need to do when all that's done is save and
display or save and return to course. Doesn't really matter. So just make sure you save as
well when you're doing that. And forgot to record this when I first did it. So you're
going to have to see it being done. So to add, I've duplicated the course. I did it as extra
time. And as I said, I belt and brace this one. So what I've done is restricted access. And I put
in student must match the following. They must have a user profile field with an email address
that is equal to LHS email address. And what that does then, this was defaulted to all learners
can see it, which is a bit odd, even if they didn't meet that condition, but I don't think they
could get in. So I've hidden entirely if student doesn't meet this condition. So if Lucy is having
options, probably best to switch that off. And then extra restrictions on attempts. Now, weirdly,
extra restrictions on attempts, I think it's misleading. So I put the password in as that. So
again, if they are an issue, so they can see it, but the password isn't working. Maybe take the
password out. Like I said, I've built and braced it just in case anyone can see it. And if someone
does for some reason that Lucian may be signed into Lucy's, then they can't access it without
that password as well. So that is adding a password in. Make sure to save it. As you go,
I've added the 57 minutes in and updated that to 57 minutes as well. Yeah, hopefully that's
helpful, mate. And hopefully that little walkthrough, feel free to share that with anyone, of course.
But yeah, again, not precious about this stuff. I'm just very familiar with it. So it was quicker
for me. Sorry that you had to waste so much time on it. Yeah, enjoy.